Juthamas Vadhanapanich

0922823821 (Mobile) iuthv@vahoo.com

Latest Position	Creative Director	W
Years(s) of Work Experience	16 years	
Latest Job Function	Web Design	N
Latest Industry Sector	Media / Publishing / Printing	W
Latest Career Level	Senior	W
Highest Education Attained	Degree	
Authorized to work in Thailand	Yes	N
Latest Salary	THB75,000	
Availability	Within Months - 1 Month	

Gender	Female
Age	37
Date of Birth	18-Aug-78
Nationality	Thailand
Marital Status	Single
Living Location	Bangkok Area - Samutprakarn
Postal Code	10130

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

Hello, I am a Creative Director, User Interface Designer and Special Lecturer. I specialize in designing and coding websites, blogging, apps, and social media plus digital marketing and SEO. A former Visual Designer at Reuters (Thailand)

I am currently working at Coconuts Media Limited as a "Creative Director" and working as a "Senior Online Marketing Executive" at House of Griffin (Part Time). I also run my own studio called Juth Studio, a group of professional web designers and web developers with extensive experience.

Lecture Experience

- "Developing Digital Contents" / School of Science and Technology, University of the Thai Chamber of Commerce / February 9, 2015
- "Multimedia Storytelling" / Graduate School, Ramkhamhaeng University / February 13, 2015
 "Social Commerce"/ Seminar / Celebrating 30 years of School of Science and Technology, University of the Thai Chamber of Commerce / May 26, 2015
- "Social Media Marketing, Adwords & SEO Secrets" / Master's Degree Students, University of the Thai Chamber of Commerce / July 26, 2015
 "Social Media Marketing, Adwords & SEO Secrets" / Master's Degree Students, Ramkhamhaeng University / August 6, 2015

- Social Media Marketing, Adwords & SEO Secrets" / Master's Degree Students, Nanishalamidality / August / Aug December 8, 2015
- Basic Responsive Web Design, Teach design and coding School of Science and Technology, University of the thai Chamber of Commerce / February 15-16, 2016

I teach English Language & Culture for kids around my neighborhood for free every Sunday morning.

I have strong aesthetic sense. I am able to combine creativity with practicality. Keep it creative, but keep it simple, keep it usable, and keep it user friendly. I am adept with typography and grid-based design principles. I am capable of taking a website from design concept to fully-functional HTML and CSS. I am standards-based designer with strong HTML5/CSS3 & Responsive Web Design skills. I hand-code well structured and clean HTML.

I have 13 years' experience of web design. I am responsible. I work fast. I love what I do. The only way to do great work is to love what you do, right?

I can design a well-constructed and easy-to-navigate website which provides great experience for visitors

I have an eye for detail. I love to improve on an original or less satisfying design. I consider my job to be producing functioning works of art. I like to trim the fat, performing liposuction on your CSS3 and HTML5 to get the most concise code. I understand that there are many ways to solve the problem but choose what is best for the client. After my suggestions, I have to tell them realistically how I am going to improve it and make it prettier.

I care the power of color. The right choice and combination of colors are as important for a website as the content and typography. Colors can contribute to a variety of experiences, and they influence the user's interpretation of the content. Colors set the mood and thus must suit the core intent of the design. A subtle and carefully thought-out color combination goes a long way.

Behance behance.net/juth Linkedin https://th.linkedin.com/in/juthy My portfolio juth.in.th My design studio juthstudio.com My blog juth.net

EDUCATION

1996 - 1999

Srinakharinwirot University, Bachelor Degree of Fine Arts (major: Visual Arts and Communications Design) Grade / GPA: 3.19

1990 - 1994

Triamudomsuksa Nomklao School, Grade 12 (major: Arts and French)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Aug / 2013 - Present Coconuts Media Ltd. THB 75.000

Lead creative sessions. Manage multiple projects from concept through completion. I am charged with determining the best ways for us to visually represent the company's identity online.

coconuts.co

tv.coconuts.co

House of Griffin

Senior Online Marketing Executive Work on the digital media and marketing, social media , onsite implementation and general design using HTML5 and CSS3. Analyze the website and business situations quickly. Develop insightful, thorough reommendations to improve technical, design, content, on-page and off-

I do flexibility, creativity, project and time management, business savvy and excellent verbal and written communications. I have experience with social media, product launches, web analytics tools (Google Analytics), search engine marketing (SEM) and search engine optimization (SEO). I am also responsible for doing SEO and Adwords. Plus I do graphic design, product design and web design.

I work here 2 days / week

page optimization elements.

Reuters Software (Thailand) Limited

Jan / 2012 - Present

THB 25,000

(Belgian universal multi-channel bank), Barclays (UK) and DBS Bank. I also design LCD TV interface (big screen on the wall) for Shenzhen Stock Exchange in China. I coordinate with product managers and programmers to ensure sitemap, flow diagrams and wireframes are properly translated to the live site. I also do the HTML5/CSS3.

The project I'm working on is "Internet Suite" the native application on iPad. The Internet Suite app allow you to view market quotes, news and charts sourced from Thomson Reuters Internet Suite (TRIS) product.

BBTV New Media Co., Ltd.

Creative Director

I created the BUGABOO character and friends. BUGABOO is the internet TV. I design the website www.bugaboo.tv BUGABOO is a mascot of

BUGABOO.TV

I re-design website for Media Studio (final design was sold at 500,000 Baht). I created the Thai Supermodel's magazine Volume 1 on iPad.

I am the head of Creative Section. I'm ultimately responsible for the quality of the final creative work in BBTV New Media.

Inspiration Area Co., Ltd.

Senior Web Designer

All digital media and offline printing. I design and do the XHTML and CSS.

For example: www.met-bangkok.com (Flash site)

Dec / 2008 - Nov / 2009 THB 36,000

Aug / 2011 - Nov / 2011

Sanook Online Limited

Senior Web Designer

Design social network website, Interface Design for widgets, Banner, Logo, T-Shirt, Microsite, Flash Ecard, E-Newsletter.

Oct / 2007 - Oct / 2008 THB 33,000

Mode 2 (Thailand) Co., Ltd.

Senior Web Designer

Design User Interface, Logo, Banner, Magazine Cover. All the works came from head office in Japan.

Jul / 2006 - Jul / 2007 THB 28,000

Fun Box Co., Ltd.

Web Designer

Design digital media and offline printing for SEAL Online, an online game from South Korea.

Dec / 2004 - Aug / 2005

THB 20,000

Phenomena Company Limited

Web Designer

Design movie websites such as www.shuttermovie.com (The official website of Shutter, the movie, played by Ananda Everingham) and Pheno.Com (company's website) and intranet interface.

Sep / 2004 - Dec / 2004 THB 20.000

JALwavs Co., Ltd. Flight Attendant

In-flight Service.

Jan / 2000 - Oct / 2002 THB 80,000

SKILLS (OPTIONAL)

Coding skill: HTML5, CSS3, Responsive Web Design

Software: Dreamweaver, PhotoShop, Illustrator, Sketch

English skill: TOEIC score 770.

I have been studying Japanese language (MN3 Course) at Technology Promotion Association (Thailand - Japan).

LANGUAGES (OPTIONAL)

Spoken: Thai, English, Japanese Written: Thai. English. Japanese

PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATIONS (OPTIONAL)

Responsive Web Design

Net Design Institute , 2015

HTML5

Net Design Institute, 2013

PHP & MvSQL

Net Design Institute , 2012

REFEREES (OPTIONAL)

Byron Winston Perry, Founder & CEO Coconuts Media Limitied

byron@coconuts.co

Dr. Mayuree Srikulwong, Lecturer, Computer Science Department, School of Science and Technology

University of the Thai Chamber of Commerce 0899772169

mayuree_sri@utcc.ac.th

Tina Phanichkul, Founder & Education Director

House of Griffin Co., Ltd.

tina@houseofgriffin.com

PERSONAL WEBSITES (OPTIONAL)

Juth's Portfolio: http://www.juth.in.th Juth Studio: http://www.juthstudio.com Juth's Blog: http://www.juth.net

Behance: http://https://www.behance.net/juth

